planetcruise.com 2017-03-17

# 

At Planet Cruise we are committed to protecting the personal information that you share with us through the Internet.  
This statement sets forth our privacy policy regarding information you provide to us through the use of our Web site. This statement also provides you with information on how to prevent your personal information from being collected or shared when you visit our web site, respond to our web-based promotions or send us an e-mail.

Planet Cruise respects the privacy of individuals and organisations that visit this web site or submit a response to any of the online surveys/forms provided. The following statement discloses the information dissemination and gathering practices for Planet Cruise.

In general, you can visit any part of the Planet Cruise website without telling us who you are, or revealing personal details. In certain circumstances we may ask you to provide personal information, voluntarily, e.g. when you join our mailing lists. We may use this information to contact you. However, we will not pass on this information to third parties without your prior permission.

Planet Cruise website is primarily an information source. Transactions are normally limited to feedback forms and opt-in registration processes, and script functionality such as search options.

We collect information about you through two principal means: through technology (for example IP addresses and cookies) and through your voluntary submission of information.</p>

We also use cookies and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information for a variety of purposes, such as to improve the design, content and navigation of our website and to enable us to provide a more personalised experience when you browse the Internet. Most industry-standard web browsers have an option that allows you to turn off all cookies or have your computer inform you each time that a request to place a cookie is being made. If you turn cookies off (or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie), you may not have access to some features on our web sites and some of our services.

Planet Cruise is not liable for information that is inaccurate due to technical defects in software used on our web sites, whether induced by our systems or by software provided by third parties.

You can use the majority of our web sites without being required to divulge any personally identifiable information to us. To participate in or use some of the activities available on our sites (such as entering a contest or contacting us) you may be required to provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and e-mail address).  
When corresponding with you via e-mail, we may use a variety of technologies, such as &quot;clear gifs&quot; or &quot;web beacons&quot;, to let us know, among other things, whether you received and opened our e-mail. The clear gif included in the e-mail may establish a cookie on your system that further allows us to tailor information to fit your personal interests.

Planet Cruise will not trade, sell or share such personally identifiable information for use by any third parties unless we have informed you, been authorised by you or are required by law to do so. The term &quot;third parties&quot; does not include any subsidiaries or affiliates of Planet Cruise, service providers or vendors acting on Planet Cruise's behalf or the purchaser of substantially all of the assets of Planet Cruise or a subsidiary or affiliate of Planet Cruise. Our policy is to require that third parties keep that information confidential. We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information, without notice, if we believe that such action is necessary to defend and protect the rights or property of Planet Cruise and its family of web sites or to protect the personal safety of users of Planet Cruise, its web sites or the public.

We use the information that you share with us for these purposes:

  * To improve the design, content and navigation of our website.
  * To measure consumer demand or interest in various offerings; and for marketing and promotional purposes, including providing you with information about products and services offered by the various Cruise Lines and Tour Operator 

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct usage of information, we monitor and adjust our physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee that data transmitted over the Internet will always be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products and services and you do so at your own risk. Upon receipt of your transmission, we strive to ensure the security of that information in our systems.

Every effort is made to ensure that downloadable files are free from defects or computer viruses. We accept no liability for any damages incurred to a user's computer system, software or data in connection with this site.

None of our web sites are targeted at children (minors under thirteen years of age) and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children who have not obtained parental consent.

Planet Cruise website contain links to other Internet sites and to resources that we believe may be useful. These links will lead you to web sites (via pop up windows) operated by third parties that operate under different privacy policies. We encourage you to review those privacy policies, as we have no control over information you may submit to those third parties.

Our web sites may use third parties, such as ad server companies, to present or serve advertisements that you may see on our web site. Our web sites may also include advertisements placed by third parties. Our privacy policy does not cover any information collected by those third parties nor does it cover how they may use such information.

Wherever possible we actively encourage all partners whose websites, home pages, advertisements, or links are co-located on our website to implement policies and practices that respect the privacy of our visitors. However, the actual privacy practices adopted by these third parties are beyond our control.

By using our web sites, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Planet Cruise reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time. Visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time to stay abreast of any changes. Your continued use of our web sites following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept those changes. This privacy policy was last modified on 21st April 2006.
